# IRUMVA HABUMUGISHA Anselme

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**



irumvanselme@outlook.com

+250 783 080 173

@irumvanselme

https://irumvanselme.is-a.dev

#### **Profile**

I am an enthusiastic, hardworking and committed individual with a proven track record of **designing and developing web Apps** and **managing databases**. I have strong technical skills, as well as excellent interpersonal skills.

I 've spent the last [4 years] helping companies, individuals, institutions and organizations increase their sales using my skills. I am eager to be challenged in order to grow and expand on the skillset I have gained through my experience in the IT sector.

# **Experience**

### **Centrika** \ Software Engineer

NOV 2021 - PRESENT, Kigali - Rwanda

I worked as a Mid Level Fullstack Software Engineer at Centrika to develop the Application for Booking Buses in Rwanda. I worked as a Backend [Spring Boot] and Mobile Developer [React Native] at this company.

#### **Korea Auto Parts** \ Software Engineer [Remote]

JUN 2018 - NOV 2022, Kigali Rwanda

I Worked as Full Stack Software Developer for this compay. I helped Increase Sales by making a customer focused ecommerce for this company. This ecomerce was developed in **[NodeJS]**, **[Nextjs[React]]** and desiged in **[Adobe XD]**. I was serving as a FullStack Engineer. Designing Backend and Frontend Development

#### Education

#### Rwanda Coding Academy

Professional Certificate of Secondary Education in Software Engineering

JUN 2018 - PRESENT, Kigali Rwanda

I got a full bucket of skills required for a Software Engineer. Including Software Programming, Embedded Systems, Network Security and other Sciences. I worked on many Projects of the Government of Rwanda as I was attending the School of Rwanda. I gained a lot of skills [Both Proffesional and Inter Personal] from this school.

# Skills (Experienced)

▶ React

Express [NodeJs]

▶ PHP Laravel

> AWS

> and many more

# Languages

> English

Kinyarwanda

Kiswahili

### **Intrests & Hobbies**

Documentaries

Table games

Cooking

### Social Media



@irumvanselme



@irumvanselme



@irumva-anselme